This is a picture of me at rock bottom.
It was Christmas Eve,
I was living at my girlfriend's parents' house
in their extra bedroom.
And I'm the guy she just met on the internet
that just quit her job for it,
that just lost everything.
My business partner took all the money I had made
from selling my gyms,
and I just found out the $100,000 that I put in
to launch this new business
was getting held up by the processor,
and I had to pay all my bills
and sent my last payment,
leaving only $1,000 left in my bank account.
And I was like, I think you should leave me.
I think I'm a sicken ship right now,
and I respect you.
We're cool if you wanna walk away,
and I would walk away from you right now.
She pulled my chin towards hers,
and she said I would sleep with you
on her bridge to Canada.
If you find a girl who believes in your dreams
more than you do,
who makes you wanna be a better man,
who's willing to work alongside you to get there,
and is grateful for whatever you have today,
just marry her.
Because at the end of the day,
your spouse marries two people,
the person you are and the person you're gonna become.
Make sure they love both.